<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vegetarian on Recipes</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/tags/vegetarian/</link><description>Recent content in vegetarian on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 21:11:51 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/tags/vegetarian/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Soft Cheese Vegetables</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/soft-cheese-vegetables/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 21:11:51 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/soft-cheese-vegetables/</guid><description>Prep Cook Serves 10 min 10 min 2-3 Ingredients 1 bunch asparagus, sliced into 4-6&amp;quot; chunks. Recommend slicing 1&amp;quot; off bottoms and composting. 1 jalapeno 1/2 lbs mushrooms 2 bell peppers, sliced Garlic and herb soft spreadable cheese (I like alouette brand) Heavy cream (Optional) bacon bits (exclude if making vegetarian version) (Optional) other veggies you enjoy! Steps Wash and chop all veggies Fry veggies in skillet over medium heat.</description></item><item><title>Banana Bread</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/banana-bread/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/banana-bread/</guid><description>Low sugar version with chocolate chips
Prep Cook Serves 30 min 50 min 1 loaf Ingredients 3-4 large super ripe bananas 2 tbsp lemon juice 1 egg 100g Fage yogurt 2 tsp melted coconut oil 50g brown sugar 2 tsp vanilla extract 150g chopped walnuts 200g flour 1 tsp baking soda 1/4 tsp salt 150g dark chocolate chips Steps Mix baking soda, salt and flour.</description></item><item><title>Erdbeertorte</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/erdbeertorte/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/erdbeertorte/</guid><description>My favorite strawberry cake, family recipe :)
Prep Cook Serves 1 hr 10 min 1 cake Ingredients 500g fresh strawberries, washed, de-stemmed, and cut in halves. Ingredients for 500mL vanilla pudding (dealers choice recipe, I like 500mL milk + 40g cornstarch + vanilla) 1 packet Tortenguss/gelatin Steps Go make the Tortenboden (cake base). Once somewhat cool, prepare the vanilla pudding and pour it into the cake base.</description></item><item><title>Gebrannte Mandeln</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/gebrannte-mandeln/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/gebrannte-mandeln/</guid><description>These are a German christmas market treat, but the recipe has some kind of a learning curve and a lot of stirring :)
Prep Cook Serves 1 hr &amp;ndash; 7 4 oz bags Ingredients 400g sugar 400 raw whole almonds 2 tsp cinnamon 2 tbsp real vanilla (imitation vanilla will do the same job) 1 oz water Steps Mix the sugar and cinnamon.</description></item><item><title>Mayonnaise</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/mayonnaise/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/mayonnaise/</guid><description>Homemade is better than store bought.
Prep Cook Serves 15 min - 1 container Ingredients 1-3 large eggs 1 tbsp Dijon mustard 2 tbsp red or white vinegar 1 tsp sugar or sweetener (optional) 1/4 tsp salt 250 ml avocado oil or light olive oil (these have proven to be the most neutral in flavor and healthier than vegetable oils) 1 tsp fresh lemon juice (optional) Steps This recipe is made the fastest with a food processor or a blender, but a good consistency can be achieved with a whisk.</description></item><item><title>Milchreis</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/milchreis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/milchreis/</guid><description>A classic German comfort food, served with sugar-cinnamon or fruit cocktail.
Prep Cook Serves 10 min 50 min 4 servings Ingredients 1 liter milk, 6 tbsp milk divided 250g rice (arborio or pearl) 2 tbsp butter 50g corn starch 2 eggs (optional) 2 tbsp vanilla extract sugar and cinnamon to taste fruit cocktail (optional) Steps Triple wash the rice and bring with milk, vanilla and butter to a quick boil, then turn down the heat for a light simmer.</description></item><item><title>Mouse au chocolate</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/choc-mousse/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/choc-mousse/</guid><description>Super quick and sugar free
Prep Chill Serves 10 min 30 min 4-6 Ingredients 1.5 cup heavy whipping cream 4 tbps heavy whipping cream 1/4 cup cocoa powder 25 g 100% cocoa baking chocolate 2 tbsp sweetener, I like purevia dark chocolate chunks, or dark baking chocolate in slivers for decoration Steps Whip heavy cream until fully thinkened and then add sweetener, vanilla and cocoa.</description></item><item><title>Tiramisu</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/tiramisu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/tiramisu/</guid><description>Low sugar version, but with coffee and alcohol
Prep Chill Serves 45 min 3+ hr 9 x 13 pan Ingredients 500 ml strong coffee or espresso (I used TJ&amp;rsquo;s instant coffee), cold 100 ml Amaretto or Hazelnut Liquor or Rum 6 packets sweetener (I use purevia) (or 30g sugar) 2 eggs (separated) 1 dash salt 1 lbs mascarpone (room temperature) 450 ml heavy cream 4 packs lady fingers (12 in each pack) cocoa for dusting 4 tbsp vanilla Steps First whip the egg whites with a dash of salt until it creates stiff peaks.</description></item><item><title>Vanillekipferl</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/vanillekipferl/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/vanillekipferl/</guid><description>German holiday shortbread cookies, nutty and dusted in powdered sugar
Prep Cook Serves 30 min 12-15 min not sure, please count when you try this recipe Ingredients 300g flour 3 eggs 80g sugar 2 tbsp vanilla extract 2 packets vanille sugar (8g per packet) 125g finely chopped almonds (pieces not bigger than a nerds candy) 250g soft butter, cut in small cubes enough powder sugar to coat the cookies Steps Combine flour, sugar, eggs and vanilla in a bowl to a soft dough.</description></item><item><title>Vanillepudding</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/vanillepudding/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/vanillepudding/</guid><description>Enjoyed hot as well as cold with your favorite mix-ins or fruit. :)
Prep Cook Serves 5 min 10 min 2 servings Ingredients 500 ml milk 2-4 tbsp sugar (optional with sugar substitute like Allulose or sucralose or splenda) 50g corn starch 2 tbsp butter 2 tbsp vanilla extract 1 egg Steps In a cup or glass combine the cornstarch with enough milk so that it will fully dissolve (ca.</description></item><item><title>Zupfkuchen</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/zupfkuchen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:02:54 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/zupfkuchen/</guid><description>Almost a cheesecake but not as sweet. My dad&amp;rsquo;s favorite.
Prep Cook Serves 1 hr 1 hr 1 cake Ingredients Dough 300g flour 150g sugar 200g butter, melted 2 eggs 40g cocoa powder 2 tsp baking powder Filling 120g sugar 3 eggs 500g greek plain yogurt (full fat) 250 ml heavy cream 1 dash salt 2 tsp real vanilla 70g butter 2 envelopes gelatin 4 tbsp corn starch Steps Mix flour, sugar, baking powder and cocoa in a large bowl.</description></item><item><title>Tzatziki</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/tzatziki/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:01:56 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/tzatziki/</guid><description>For gyros, baked potatoes, and raclette.
Prep Cook Serves 30 min 0 min 2-3 cups Ingredients 1 big cucumber (or two small ones) 1 container (454g) full-fat greek yogurt (I like Fage 5%) 1 container sour cream (only dairy, no other additives) 1 1/2 tbsp garlic powder 3 tbsp dried dill 1/2 tsp salt 1 tsp sugar (optional) Steps Shred the cucumber into a bowl with the finest setting on a grater.</description></item><item><title>Schweizer Knoten</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/schweizer-knoten/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/schweizer-knoten/</guid><description>Small, fancy dinner rolls
Prep Bake Serves 2 hr 20 min 20-24 rolls Ingredients 1/2 stick butter (60g), softened 250 ml milk 2 egg 500 g flour 1.5 tsp salt 3 tbsp sugar 3 tbsp dry yeast 60 g whole flax seeds 60 g whole sunflower seeds Steps Mix very soft butter with luke warm milk and 1 egg in a large bowl.</description></item></channel></rss>