<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Recipes</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Recipes</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 21:39:55 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Dry Rub</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/dry-rub/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 21:39:55 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/dry-rub/</guid><description>For grilling, frying, and slow-cooking meats.
Prep Cook Serves 10 min 0 min 2 cups Ingredients 1/2 to 1 cup brown sugar 1/2 cup kosher salt (we use Diamond Crystal kosher salt) 4 tablespoons smoked paprika 2 tablespoons coarse black pepper 1/2 tablespoon cumin 1/2 tablespoon onion powder 1/2 tablespoon garlic powder 1 teaspoon cayenne pepper Steps Combine all ingredients, and store in an airtight container.</description></item><item><title>Soft Cheese Vegetables</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/soft-cheese-vegetables/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 21:11:51 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/soft-cheese-vegetables/</guid><description>Prep Cook Serves 10 min 10 min 2-3 Ingredients 1 bunch asparagus, sliced into 4-6&amp;quot; chunks. Recommend slicing 1&amp;quot; off bottoms and composting. 1 jalapeno 1/2 lbs mushrooms 2 bell peppers, sliced Garlic and herb soft spreadable cheese (I like alouette brand) Heavy cream (Optional) bacon bits (exclude if making vegetarian version) (Optional) other veggies you enjoy! Steps Wash and chop all veggies Fry veggies in skillet over medium heat.</description></item><item><title>Raclette</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/raclette/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 21:04:59 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/raclette/</guid><description>Prep Cook Serves 3 hr 0 min 6-8 Ingredients (toppings) Chopped onion Peas/corn Carne asada Meatballs Teriyaki chicken Pineapple Diced ham Tzatziki Cheese (raclette cheese or swiss are best) Chopped bell peppers Small cooked noodles Sliced mushrooms Butter Bacon Potatoes Steps Prep all of the toppings into bowls. This can be done in the morning and then save the toppings for the evening.</description></item><item><title>Mexican Rice</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/mexican-rice/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 May 2021 20:34:06 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/mexican-rice/</guid><description>Prep Cook Serves 10min 20min 4 Ingredients 1 3/4 cups + 2 Tbsp warm water or unsalted chicken broth 1 medium roma tomato, minced (heaping 1/3 cup) 2 1/2 tsp Caldo de Tomate (not vegetarian) 1/2 tsp onion powder 1/4 tsp chili powder 1/4 tsp freshly ground black pepper 1 Tbsp olive oil or vegetable oil 1 cup uncooked long grain white rice 1 large garlic clove, minced 1 1/2 tsp) Steps Whisk together warm water, minced tomato, Caldo de Tomate, onion powder, chili powder, and black pepper.</description></item><item><title>Banana Bread</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/banana-bread/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/banana-bread/</guid><description>Low sugar version with chocolate chips
Prep Cook Serves 30 min 50 min 1 loaf Ingredients 3-4 large super ripe bananas 2 tbsp lemon juice 1 egg 100g Fage yogurt 2 tsp melted coconut oil 50g brown sugar 2 tsp vanilla extract 150g chopped walnuts 200g flour 1 tsp baking soda 1/4 tsp salt 150g dark chocolate chips Steps Mix baking soda, salt and flour.</description></item><item><title>Erdbeertorte</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/erdbeertorte/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/erdbeertorte/</guid><description>My favorite strawberry cake, family recipe :)
Prep Cook Serves 1 hr 10 min 1 cake Ingredients 500g fresh strawberries, washed, de-stemmed, and cut in halves. Ingredients for 500mL vanilla pudding (dealers choice recipe, I like 500mL milk + 40g cornstarch + vanilla) 1 packet Tortenguss/gelatin Steps Go make the Tortenboden (cake base). Once somewhat cool, prepare the vanilla pudding and pour it into the cake base.</description></item><item><title>Gebrannte Mandeln</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/gebrannte-mandeln/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/gebrannte-mandeln/</guid><description>These are a German christmas market treat, but the recipe has some kind of a learning curve and a lot of stirring :)
Prep Cook Serves 1 hr &amp;ndash; 7 4 oz bags Ingredients 400g sugar 400 raw whole almonds 2 tsp cinnamon 2 tbsp real vanilla (imitation vanilla will do the same job) 1 oz water Steps Mix the sugar and cinnamon.</description></item><item><title>Mayonnaise</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/mayonnaise/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/mayonnaise/</guid><description>Homemade is better than store bought.
Prep Cook Serves 15 min - 1 container Ingredients 1-3 large eggs 1 tbsp Dijon mustard 2 tbsp red or white vinegar 1 tsp sugar or sweetener (optional) 1/4 tsp salt 250 ml avocado oil or light olive oil (these have proven to be the most neutral in flavor and healthier than vegetable oils) 1 tsp fresh lemon juice (optional) Steps This recipe is made the fastest with a food processor or a blender, but a good consistency can be achieved with a whisk.</description></item><item><title>Milchreis</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/milchreis/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/milchreis/</guid><description>A classic German comfort food, served with sugar-cinnamon or fruit cocktail.
Prep Cook Serves 10 min 50 min 4 servings Ingredients 1 liter milk, 6 tbsp milk divided 250g rice (arborio or pearl) 2 tbsp butter 50g corn starch 2 eggs (optional) 2 tbsp vanilla extract sugar and cinnamon to taste fruit cocktail (optional) Steps Triple wash the rice and bring with milk, vanilla and butter to a quick boil, then turn down the heat for a light simmer.</description></item><item><title>Mouse au chocolate</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/choc-mousse/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/choc-mousse/</guid><description>Super quick and sugar free
Prep Chill Serves 10 min 30 min 4-6 Ingredients 1.5 cup heavy whipping cream 4 tbps heavy whipping cream 1/4 cup cocoa powder 25 g 100% cocoa baking chocolate 2 tbsp sweetener, I like purevia dark chocolate chunks, or dark baking chocolate in slivers for decoration Steps Whip heavy cream until fully thinkened and then add sweetener, vanilla and cocoa.</description></item><item><title>Tiramisu</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/tiramisu/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/tiramisu/</guid><description>Low sugar version, but with coffee and alcohol
Prep Chill Serves 45 min 3+ hr 9 x 13 pan Ingredients 500 ml strong coffee or espresso (I used TJ&amp;rsquo;s instant coffee), cold 100 ml Amaretto or Hazelnut Liquor or Rum 6 packets sweetener (I use purevia) (or 30g sugar) 2 eggs (separated) 1 dash salt 1 lbs mascarpone (room temperature) 450 ml heavy cream 4 packs lady fingers (12 in each pack) cocoa for dusting 4 tbsp vanilla Steps First whip the egg whites with a dash of salt until it creates stiff peaks.</description></item><item><title>Vanillekipferl</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/vanillekipferl/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/vanillekipferl/</guid><description>German holiday shortbread cookies, nutty and dusted in powdered sugar
Prep Cook Serves 30 min 12-15 min not sure, please count when you try this recipe Ingredients 300g flour 3 eggs 80g sugar 2 tbsp vanilla extract 2 packets vanille sugar (8g per packet) 125g finely chopped almonds (pieces not bigger than a nerds candy) 250g soft butter, cut in small cubes enough powder sugar to coat the cookies Steps Combine flour, sugar, eggs and vanilla in a bowl to a soft dough.</description></item><item><title>Vanillepudding</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/vanillepudding/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:03:18 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/vanillepudding/</guid><description>Enjoyed hot as well as cold with your favorite mix-ins or fruit. :)
Prep Cook Serves 5 min 10 min 2 servings Ingredients 500 ml milk 2-4 tbsp sugar (optional with sugar substitute like Allulose or sucralose or splenda) 50g corn starch 2 tbsp butter 2 tbsp vanilla extract 1 egg Steps In a cup or glass combine the cornstarch with enough milk so that it will fully dissolve (ca.</description></item><item><title>Zupfkuchen</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/zupfkuchen/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:02:54 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/zupfkuchen/</guid><description>Almost a cheesecake but not as sweet. My dad&amp;rsquo;s favorite.
Prep Cook Serves 1 hr 1 hr 1 cake Ingredients Dough 300g flour 150g sugar 200g butter, melted 2 eggs 40g cocoa powder 2 tsp baking powder Filling 120g sugar 3 eggs 500g greek plain yogurt (full fat) 250 ml heavy cream 1 dash salt 2 tsp real vanilla 70g butter 2 envelopes gelatin 4 tbsp corn starch Steps Mix flour, sugar, baking powder and cocoa in a large bowl.</description></item><item><title>Biskuitboden</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/biskuitboden/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:02:33 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/biskuitboden/</guid><description>Simple family recipe for a cake base, usually topped with fruits. See Erdbeertorte.
Prep Cook Serves 10 min 25 min 1 cake base Ingredients 4 eggs 120g sugar (can halve if desired) 120g flour 1tsp baking powder Steps Separate eggs from yolks (save both). In a glass or metal bowl, beat the egg whites until stiff peaks form, adding the sugar slowly as you go.</description></item><item><title>Tzatziki</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/tzatziki/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:01:56 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/tzatziki/</guid><description>For gyros, baked potatoes, and raclette.
Prep Cook Serves 30 min 0 min 2-3 cups Ingredients 1 big cucumber (or two small ones) 1 container (454g) full-fat greek yogurt (I like Fage 5%) 1 container sour cream (only dairy, no other additives) 1 1/2 tbsp garlic powder 3 tbsp dried dill 1/2 tsp salt 1 tsp sugar (optional) Steps Shred the cucumber into a bowl with the finest setting on a grater.</description></item><item><title>BBQ Sauce</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/bbq-sauce/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 09:01:40 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/bbq-sauce/</guid><description>No-ketchup recipe.
Prep Cook Serves 5 min 10 min 2 cups Ingredients 1 can (15 ounces) tomato sauce 1 can (6 ounces) tomato paste 1/3 cup apple cider vinegar 1/4 cup pure maple syrup 1/4 cup molasses 2 tablespoons Worcestershire sauce 2 teaspoons smoked paprika 1 teaspoon dry mustard 1 teaspoon garlic powder 1/2 teaspoon kosher salt 1/2 teaspoon black pepper 1/8-1/4 teaspoon cayenne pepper (to taste) Steps In a medium saucepan, stir together all of the ingredients: tomato sauce, tomato paste, apple cider vinegar, maple syrup, molasses, Worcestershire, smoked paprika, dry mustard, garlic, salt, black pepper, and cayenne pepper.</description></item><item><title>Pork Chashu</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/pork-chashu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 22:29:42 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/pork-chashu/</guid><description>Also known as pork belly. Great with tonkotsu ramen.
Prep Cook Serves 20 min 6 hr 4 Ingredients 500 g pork belly, skin on 1/2 cup japanese soy sauce 4 slices ginger 1 cup water 1/2 cup cooking sake (Japanese rice wine) 4 garlic, crushed 1 leek 1/2 cup mirin Steps Roll up the pork belly with the skin side out.</description></item><item><title>Pork Bao</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/pork-bao/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 12:49:58 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/pork-bao/</guid><description>Prep Cook Serves 3 hr 30 min 10 buns Ingredients Bun dough 1 teaspoon active dry yeast ¾ cup warm water 2 cups all-purpose flour 1 cup cornstarch 5 tablespoons sugar 1/4 cup canola or vegetable oil 2 1/2 teaspoons baking powder 1-2 teaspoons water (optional) Filling 1 tablespoon oil 1/3 cup shallots or red onion (finely chopped) 1 tablespoon sugar 1 tablespoon light soy sauce 1 1/2 tablespoons oyster sauce 2 teaspoons sesame oil 2 teaspoons dark soy sauce 1/2 cup chicken stock 2 tablespoons all purpose flour 1 1/2 cups diced Chinese roast pork Steps In the bowl of an electric mixer fitted with a dough hook attachment (you can also just use a regular mixing bowl and knead by hand), dissolve the yeast in the warm water.</description></item><item><title>Baked Mac and Cheese</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/baked-mac-and-cheese/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 12:49:45 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/baked-mac-and-cheese/</guid><description>Prep Cook Serves 30 min 30 min 12 Ingredients 16 oz elbow macaroni 1 tbsp extra virgin olive oil 6 tbsp unsalted butter 1/3 cup all purpose flour 3 cups whole milk 1 cup heavy whipping cream 4 cups sharp cheddar cheese shredded 2 cups Gruyere cheese shredded salt and pepper to taste 1 1/2 cups panko crumbs 4 tbsp butter melted 1/2 cup Parmesan cheese shredded 1/4 tsp smoked paprika (or regular paprika) Steps Preheat oven to 350F.</description></item><item><title>Carnitas</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/carnitas/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 12:49:15 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/carnitas/</guid><description>Prep Cook Serves 30min 6-8hr 12 Mexican pulled pork, great on toasted buns and in burritos.
Ingredients 1 to 2 tablespoons fat or oil for skillet 4 pounds boneless pork shoulder, cut into two equal pieces 2 cups barbecue sauce, divided, plus more for serving 1/2 cup water Steps Brown pork in a skillet on both sides, about 3 minutes per side.</description></item><item><title>Pork Tonkotsu Ramen</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/pork-tonkotsu-ramen/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 12:49:01 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/pork-tonkotsu-ramen/</guid><description>Prep Cook Serves a lot 12-18 hr 6 Ingredients Broth: 8 lbs pork bones (neck or femur) 0.8 lbs pork fatback/suet Tare: 5 3 inch by 3 inch squares of kombu. Shredded kombu or knots will do in a pinch but will be annoying. Water to cover (around 1-2 cups) ¾ cup dried niboshi (can sub dried anchovies if niboshi not available) 1 tbs sesame oil 1 cup loosely packed bonito ¼ cup sake ¼ cup mirin 1 cup soy sauce Salt to taste Steps Broth: Before any cooking, soak the bones in cold water in a large, non-reactive vessel, for at least 6 hours, and up to 24 hours.</description></item><item><title>Beef Bourguignon</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/beef-bourguignon/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 12:48:16 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/beef-bourguignon/</guid><description>Also known as pot roast.
Prep Cook Serves 1 hr 20 min 9 hr 6 Ingredients 6 slices bacon finely chopped 3 pounds boneless beef chuck cut to 1 inch cubes 1 cup red cooking wine 2 cups chicken broth 1/2 cup tomato sauce 1/4 cup soy sauce 1/4 cup flour 3 garlic cloves finely chopped 2 tablespoons thyme finely chopped 5 medium carrots sliced 1 pound baby potatoes 8 ounces fresh mushrooms sliced fresh chopped parsley for garnish Steps In a large skillet cook bacon over medium high heat until crisp.</description></item><item><title>Udon Stir Fry</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/udon-stir-fry/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 12:48:01 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/udon-stir-fry/</guid><description>Prep Cook Serves 30 min 30 min 6 Ingredients 2 tablespoons vegetable oil, divided 4 cups very coarsely chopped green cabbage (from about ¼ medium - head) 2 7-ounce packages instant udon noodles, flavor packets discarded 2 teaspoons toasted sesame oil 8 ounces ground pork 5 scallions, white and pale-green parts coarsely chopped, - dark-green parts thinly sliced 2 teaspoons finely grated fresh ginger (from a 1-inch knob) 1 teaspoon crushed red pepper flakes ⅓ cup mirin ⅓ cup soy sauce 1 tablespoon toasted sesame seeds, plus more for serving Steps Heat 1 Tbsp.</description></item><item><title>Lamb Gyros</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/gyros/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 12:47:48 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/gyros/</guid><description>Prep Cook Serves 1 hr 15 min 35 min 6 Ingredients Gyro Meat 1 pound ground lamb 2 teaspoons kosher salt ½ teaspoon freshly ground black pepper 2 tablespoons fresh oregano leaves ½ yellow onion (cut into 1-inch chunks) 1 clove garlic (sliced) 3 ounces slab bacon (or 5 slices sliced bacon, cut into ½-inch pieces) To serve Pocketless pita bread Tzatziki sauce Tomato (coarsely chopped) Yellow onion (thinly sliced) Steps Make the Gyro Meat: In a medium bowl, combine the ground lamb, salt, pepper and oregano leaves with your hands, mixing until all of the seasonings have been evenly distributed.</description></item><item><title>No-Noodle Lasagna</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/no-noodle-lasagna/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 12:47:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/no-noodle-lasagna/</guid><description>Prep Cook Serves 30 min 1.5 hr 12 (one 9x13&amp;quot; pan) Ingredients &amp;ldquo;Noodles&amp;rdquo; 4 large eggs 8 oz cream cheese, softened 2/4 cup Parmesan cheese, grated 2 1/2 cup mozzarella cheese, shredded 1/2 tsp Italian seasoning 1/2 tsp garlic powder 1/2 tsp onion powder Filling 2 lb ground beef 3 cups marinara sauce, divided 1 1/2 cup mozzarella cheese, shredded 3/4 tbsp whole milk ricotta cheese 2 tbsp minced onion flakes 2 tsp dried oregano 2 tsp garlic powder 2 tsp dried basil 2 tsp Italian seasoning Steps &amp;ldquo;Noodles&amp;rdquo; Preheat oven to 375°F.</description></item><item><title>Burritos</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/burritos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 12:46:59 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/burritos/</guid><description>Prep Cook Serves 5min 2min depends Ingredients Carnitas or carne asada Mexican rice Tortillas Sour cream (Tillamook kind is great) Pico de Gallo Mexican blend cheese Steps Warm tortillas in skillet or in oven, optionally melting cheese on it Assemble and roll up tortilla with filling Place rolled-up burrito back in skillet on the seam, so that it &amp;ldquo;grills shut&amp;rdquo; Keep burrito in pan until desired tortilla crispiness is achieved Notes Oversized tortillas will make the burrito-rolling exponentially easier, but personally I like the taste better with the standard size.</description></item><item><title>Carne Asada</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/carne-asada/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 12:46:31 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/carne-asada/</guid><description>Prep Cook Serves 2hr 15min 10hr 5 Ingredients 1/4 cup olive oil 1/4 cup fresh orange juice 1 tsp lime zest 1/4 cup fresh lime juice 1 - 3 canned chipotle peppers, to taste, minced 1 Tbsp adobo sauce from can of chipotle peppers 1 Tbsp chili powder 1 Tbsp ancho chili powder 1 1/2 Tbsp minced fresh garlic 1/2 cup chopped cilantro 1 1/2 tsp ground cumin 1/2 tsp ground coriander 1 1/2 tsp granulated sugar Salt and freshly ground black pepper 2 lbs flank steak or skirt steak Steps Make marinade: In a mixing bowl whisk together olive oil, orange juice, lime zest, lime juice, chipotle pepper, adobo sauce, chili powder, ancho chili powder, garlic, cilantro, cumin, coriander and sugar.</description></item><item><title>Butter Chicken</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/butter-chicken/</link><pubDate>Mon, 24 May 2021 12:33:09 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/butter-chicken/</guid><description>Also known as murgh makhani.
Prep Cook Serves 30 min 1.5 hr 6 Ingredients Marinade 28 oz (800g) boneless and skinless chicken thighs or breasts cut into bite-sized pieces 1/2 cup plain yogurt 1 1/2 tablespoons minced garlic 1 tablespoon minced ginger (or finely grated) 2 teaspoons garam masala 1 teaspoon turmeric 1 teaspoon ground cumin 1 teaspoon red chili powder 1 teaspoon of salt Sauce 1 large onion, sliced or chopped 1 1/2 tablespoons garlic, minced 1 tablespoon ginger, minced or finely grated 1 1/2 teaspoons ground cumin 1 1/2 teaspoons garam masala 1 teaspoon ground coriander 14 oz (400 g) crushed tomatoes 1 teaspoon red chili powder (adjust to your taste preference) 1 1/4 teaspoons salt (or to taste) 1 cup of heavy cream 1 tablespoon sugar 1/2 teaspoon kasoori methi (or dried fenugreek leaves) Steps In a bowl, combine chicken with the marinade; let marinate for 30 minutes to an hour (or overnight if time allows).</description></item><item><title>Schweizer Knoten</title><link>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/schweizer-knoten/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://mirrorkey.dev/recipes/posts/schweizer-knoten/</guid><description>Small, fancy dinner rolls
Prep Bake Serves 2 hr 20 min 20-24 rolls Ingredients 1/2 stick butter (60g), softened 250 ml milk 2 egg 500 g flour 1.5 tsp salt 3 tbsp sugar 3 tbsp dry yeast 60 g whole flax seeds 60 g whole sunflower seeds Steps Mix very soft butter with luke warm milk and 1 egg in a large bowl.</description></item></channel></rss>